Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - E-H
        - Grant, Eddy - The killer at his best - all the hits, 1984; SR-26433; Grant, Eddy (Box 35)
          Catalog # BGI 1000; A-side Matrix # C-146106-A B911000A
          ICE
          Barbados
        - Grant, Eddy - Born tuff, 1986; SR-26434; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          Catalog # R 40284; A-side Matrix # AL-40284-1D
          Portrait
        - Grant, Eddy - Walking on sunshine, 1978; SR-26435; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          Catalog # JE 36244; A-side Matrix # AL-36244 1A
        - Grant, Eddy - Live at Notting Hill (Disc one), 1981; SR-26436; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26437. Double album.
          Catalog # ICELP 22; A-side Matrix # ICELP 22 A-1U
        - Grant, Eddy - Live at Notting Hill (Disc two), 1981; SR-26437; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26436. Double album.
          Catalog # ICELP 22; A-side Matrix # ICELP 22 C-1U
        - Grant, Eddy - My turn to love you, 1980; SR-26438; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26439. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JE 36522; A-side Matrix # AL-36522-1A
        - Grant, Eddy - My turn to love you, 1980; SR-26439; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26438. 2 copies.
        - Grant, Eddy - Killer on the rampage, 1982; SR-26440; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          Catalog # ICELP 3023; A-side Matrix # ICELP 3023 A-1U-1-1-1-14
        - Grant, Eddy - Live at Notting Hill (Disc one), 1982; SR-26441; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26442. Double album.
          Catalog # AIC/241705; A-side Matrix # AIC 241705 1L
          Italy
        - Grant, Eddy - Live at Notting Hill (Disc two), 1982; SR-26442; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26441. Double album.
          Catalog # AIC/241705; A-side Matrix # AIC 241705 3L
        - Grant, Eddy - File under rock, 1988; SR-26443; Grant, Eddy (Box 36)
          Catalog # 064-79 0343 1; A-side Matrix # 790343 1-A1
          Parlophone
        - Grant, Rudy - Harrison's cave Barbados, 1982; SR-26444; Grant, Rudy (Box 36)
          Catalog # SEA 1LP; A-side Matrix # SEA+1+LP+A
          Seara Records
        - Gray, Chris - Intelligent emotions EP, 1997; SR-26445; Gray, Chris (Box 36)
          Catalog # FMD 007; A-side Matrix # FMD 007-A1
          Fragmented Records
        - Greaves, R. B. - R. B. Greaves, 1977; SR-26446; Greaves, R. B. (Box 36)
          Catalog # BB 3333; A-side Matrix # BB 3333 A-P RC-1-1-11
          Bareback Records, Inc.
        - Green, Al - Tokyo…live! (Disc one), 1981; SR-26447; Green, Al (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26448. Double album.
          Catalog # 426005; A-side Matrix # 426005 A1
          Cream Records
        - Green, Al - Tokyo…live! (Disc two), 1981; SR-26448; Green, Al (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26447. Double album.
          Catalog # 426005; A-side Matrix # 426005 B1
        - Green, Al - Have a good time, 1976; SR-26449; Green, Al (Box 36)
          Catalog # SLH 32103; A-side Matrix # SLH-703 BEST
          Hi Records
        - Green, Al - Soul survivor, 1987; SR-26450; Green, Al (Box 36)
          Catalog # SP-5150; A-side Matrix # SPO-5150-A ESI
        - Green, Jesse - Nice and slow, 1976; SR-26451; Green, Jesse (Box 36)
          Catalog # EMC 3164; A-side Matrix # YAX 5237-2
          EMI Records Ltd.
          Middlesex, United Kingdom
        - Green, Jesse - 1,2,3 vamos, 1981; SR-26452; Green, Jesse (Box 36)
          Catalog # 17.2625/0; A-side Matrix # 17.2625.A.IN`
          Red Bus Records
        - Gregory D - D rules the nation, 1989; SR-26453; Gregory D; DJ Mannie Fresh (Box 36)
          Catalog # X-101-1; A-side Matrix # S-23181 X101 A
          Yo! Records
          Dallas, Texas
        - Grey and Hanks - You fooled me, 1978; SR-26454; Grey and Hanks (Box 36)
          Catalog # AFL1-3069; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3069-A 1S F1
        - Grey and Hanks - Prime time, 1980; SR-26455; Grey and Hanks (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26456. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AFL1-3477; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3477-A-1s
        - Grey and Hanks - Prime time, 1980; SR-26456; Grey and Hanks (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26455. 2 copies.
        - Grey and Hanks - Gotta put something in, 1978; SR-26457; Grey and Hanks (Box 36)
          Catalog # JT-11582; A-side Matrix # PD-11582 AIS F1
        - Griff, KW - Time of my life, 2003; SR-26458; Griff, KW (Box 36)
          Catalog # QR-042; A-side Matrix # QR-042 A
          Quiet Records
          Maryland
        - Griff, KW | DJ Patrick - Lil John (Remix); Respect; And I say to myself; Klap yo hands, 2003; SR-26459; Griff, KW; DJ Patrick; Mr. Motts (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26460. 2 copies.
          Catalog # QR-043; A-side Matrix # QR-043 A
        - Griff, KW | DJ Patrick - Lil John (Remix); Respect; And I say to myself; Klap yo hands, 2003; SR-26460; Griff, KW; DJ Patrick; Mr. Motts (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26459. 2 copies.
        - Griffin, Billy - Respect, 1983; SR-26461; Griffin, Billy (Box 36)
          Catalog # FC 38924; A-side Matrix # PAL-38924-1B
        - Griffin, Billy - Respect, 1983; SR-26462; Griffin, Billy (Box 36)
          Catalog # FC 38924; A-side Matrix # PAL-38924-1A
        - Griffin, Billy - Hold me tighter in the rain, 1982; SR-26463; Griffin, Billy (Box 36)
          Catalog # AS 1507; A-side Matrix # XSS 169046-1A
        - Groove Armada - Vertigo (Disc one), 1999; SR-26464; Groove Armada (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26465. Double album.
          Catalog # 0530331; A-side Matrix # 0530331-C
          Pepper Records
        - Groove Armada - Vertigo (Disc two), 1999; SR-26465; Groove Armada (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26464. Double album.
          Catalog # 0530331; A-side Matrix # 0530331-A1
        - Groove Armada - If everybody looked the same, 1999; SR-26466; Groove Armada (Box 36)
          Catalog # 0530290; A-side Matrix # DMM GROOVET-001P-A2
        - Groove Armada - I see you baby, 1999; SR-26467; Groove Armada; Gram'ma Funk; Fatboy Slim; Futureshock (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26468. Different discs.
          Catalog # 9230000; A-side Matrix # 0530430-4-1
        - Groove Armada - The Beligian remixes, 2000; SR-26468; Groove Armada (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26467. Different discs.
          Catalog # ZOM 013; A-side Matrix # ZOMBA-GROOVE ARMADA-"I SEE YOU BABY"(MARIUS CLUB MIX) (REMIXES)
          Jive
        - Groove Park - Say what!, 1996; SR-26469; Groove Park (Box 36)
          Catalog # SVDJ001; A-side Matrix # DFI 96-9 SVDJ 001 AI
          Silicon Valley
        - Gucci Crew II - So def, so fresh, so stupid, 1987; SR-26470; Gucci Crew II (Box 36)
          Catalog # HTLP 3303; A-side Matrix # HTLP-3303-A
          Gucci Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Groove Theory - Groove Theory (Disc one), 1995; SR-26471; Groove Theory (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26472. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 57421; A-side Matrix # 67257-A
        - Groove Theory - Groove Theory (Disc two), 1995; SR-26472; Groove Theory (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26471. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 57421; A-side Matrix # 67258-A
        - Groovkidz - Feel this way and Blowin' your mind, 1997; SR-26473; Groovkidz; Cloud 10 (Box 36)
          Repress
          Catalog # JFR003; A-side Matrix # BOOT-E
          Just Funkin Records
          Florida
        - Gross, Henry - What's in a name, 1981; SR-26474; Gross, Henry (Box 36)
          Catalog # ST-12113; A-side Matrix # ST 1 12113 24 -1
        - Guess Who - The best of Guess Who, 1971; SR-26475; Guess Who (Box 36)
          Catalog # AYL1-3662; A-side Matrix # AYL1 3662A
        - Guru - Watch what you say, 1995; SR-26476; Guru; Khan, Chaka (Box 36)
          Catalog # 12COOL 308; A-side Matrix # 12 COOL 308 A-01-1-1
          Cooltempo
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Ain't nothin' goin' on but the rent, 1986; SR-26477; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 36)
          Catalog # 885 106-1; A-side Matrix # 885-106-1-AS-DJ-ES
        - Guthrie, Gwen - It should have been you, 1982; SR-26478; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26479. Different discs.
          Catalog # 12WIP 6757; A-side Matrix # 12 WIP 6757 A-1U
        - Guthrie, Gwen - It should have been you, 1982; SR-26479; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26478. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 344; A-side Matrix # STDM 43013-1
        - Guy - Guy, 1988; SR-26480; Guy (Box 36)
          Catalog # MCA-42176; A-side Matrix # MCA-7794-FW1
        - Gypseymen - House hitz, 1992; SR-26481; Gypseymen; PM Dawn; Precious Red (Box 36)
          Catalog # HHZ-504; A-side Matrix # HHZ-504-A
          House Hitz
        - Gyrlz - Love me or leave me, 1988; SR-26482; Gyrlz (Box 36)
          Catalog # C1-90766; A-side Matrix # C1-1-90766-Z2
        - H-town - Beggin' after dark (Disc one), 1994; SR-26483; H-town (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26484. Double album.
          Catalog # PRXR-212-1; A-side Matrix # XR-212-1
          Luke Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - H-town - Beggin' after dark (Disc two), 1994; SR-26484; H-town (Box 36)
          In same jacket as # SR-26483. Double album.
          Catalog # PRXR-212-2; A-side Matrix # XR-212-2
        - Hagen, Nina - In ekstasy, 1985; SR-26485; Hagen, Nina (Box 36)
          Catalog # BFC 40004; A-side Matrix # AL 40004-1A
        - Hagen, Nina - Nunsexmonkrock, 1982; SR-26486; Hagen, Nina (Box 36)
          Signed to Bam by Hagen
          Catalog # CBS 85774; A-side Matrix # O1-85774-2A-1 AL-38008-2
        - Haig, Paul - The warp of pure fun, 1985; SR-26487; Haig, Paul (Box 36)
          Catalog # TWI 669; A-side Matrix # TWI 669 A
          Les Disques du Crepuscule
          Belgium
        - Hall, Daryl - Ooh yeah!, 1988; SR-26488; Hall, Daryl; Oates, John (Box 36)
          Catalog # AL-8539; A-side Matrix # AL-8539-SA
        - Hall, Delores - I can't live without your love, 1979; SR-26489; Hall, Delores (Box 36)
          Catalog # SPRO-9228; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9228 (9031-A)-Z1
        - Eramus Hall - Gohead, 1984; SR-26490; Eramus Hall (Box 36)
          Catalog # ST-12376; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12376 F2
        - Hall, Jimmy - Touch you, 1980; SR-26491; Hall, Jimmy (Box 36)
          Catalog # NJE 36516; A-side Matrix # AL-36516-1F
        - Halloween - Lady Midnight, 1979; SR-26492; Halloween (Box 36)
          Catalog # MK-113; A-side Matrix # MK-113-A-1-1-1
        - Halloween - Come see what it's all about, 1979; SR-26493; Halloween (Box 37)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3801; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3801-A-2 PRC-E-11-1
        - Hammond, Johnny - Storm warning, 1977; SR-26494; Hammond, Johnny (Box 37)
          Catalog # M-9076; A-side Matrix # M-9076-A-Re1 1B
          Milestone Records
        - Hancock, Herbie - Lite me up, 1982; SR-26495; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # FC 37928; A-side Matrix # PAL 37928-1A
        - Hancock, Herbie - Go for it, 1980; SR-26496; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # AS 751; A-side Matrix # XSS 167301-1D
        - Hancock, Herbie - Sound-system, 1984; SR-26497; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # FC 39478; A-side Matrix # AL-39478-1A
        - Hancock, Herbie - Monster, 1980; SR-26498; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # JC 36415; A-side Matrix # PAL 36415-1C
        - Hancock, Herbie - Man-child, 1975; SR-26499; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # PC 33812; A-side Matrix # PAL 33812-1F
        - Hancock, Herbie - Mr. Hands, 1980; SR-26500; Hancock, Herbie (Box 37)
          Catalog # BL 36578; A-side Matrix # P BL 36578-1BF
        - Handy, John - Where go the boats, 1978; SR-26501; Handy, John (Box 37)
          Catalog # BSK 3170; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3170-LW1
        - Hanson & Davis - Can't stop, 1987; SR-26502; Hanson & Davis (Box 37)
          Catalog # LPRE-004; A-side Matrix # LPRE-4-X
        - Hansen, Randy - Randy Hansen, 1980; SR-26503; Hansen, Randy (Box 37)
          Catalog # ST-12119; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12119-24
        - Harari - Harari, 1982; SR-26504; Harari (Box 37)
          Catalog # SP-6-4887; A-side Matrix # SP-06-4887A(RE-1)-P1
        - Hard Hop Heathen - Ohterior motive, 1995; SR-26505; Hard Hop Heathen (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26506. Different discs.
          Catalog # TR002; A-side Matrix # 9505X03/9705x46 A A+R-TR002
          Tricked Out Recordings
        - Hard Hop Heathen - Pure havoc; Crystal jelly, 1996; SR-26506; Hard Hop Heathen (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26505. Different discs.
          Catalog # TR006; A-side Matrix # TR-006-A
        - Hardfloor - Mahogany roots, 1997; SR-26507; Hardfloor (Box 37)
          Catalog # EYEUK021; A-side Matrix # EYEUK021XA1
          Eye Q (UK)
        - Hardkiss, Scott - God within Raincry remixes, 2000; SR-26508; Hardkiss, Scott; Jondi & Spesh (Box 37)
          Catalog # DOR 015; A-side Matrix # DOR 015 A
          Dorigen Music
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Hardy Hard - Metal hammer, 1997; SR-26509; Hardy Hard (Box 37)
          Catalog # 74321 511 671; A-side Matrix # 743 215 116 71-A1
          Loud & Slow
        - Harris, Allen - Oceans between us, 1978; SR-26510; Harris, Allen; Allen Harris Band (Box 37)
          Catalog # JC 35364; A-side Matrix # AL 35364-4A
        - Harris, Major - All my life, 1983; SR-26511; Harris, Major (Box 37)
          Catalog # PA 1401; A-side Matrix # PA-1401-A
        - Harris, Simon - Beats, breaks & scratches, 1987; SR-21280; Harris, Simon (Box 37)
          Catalog # MOMIX 1; A-side Matrix # MOMIX 1-A-X
        - Harris, Simon - Beats, breaks & scratches volume 2, 1988; SR-21281; Harris, Simon (Box 37)
          Catalog # MOMIX 2; A-side Matrix # WHAT'S THE FIRST SINGLE? MOMIX-2-A
        - Harris, Simon - Beats, breaks & scratches volume 4, 1989; SR-21282; Harris, Simon (Box 37)
          Catalog # MOMIX 4; A-side Matrix # WHAT'S THE FIRST SINGLE? MOMIX-4-A 2
        - Harry, Debbie - KooKoo, 1981; SR-26512; Harry, Debbie (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26513. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CHR 1347; A-side Matrix # CHR 1347 AS-10
          Chrysalis Records Inc.
        - Harry, Debbie - KooKoo, 1981; SR-26513; Harry, Debbie (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26512. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CHR 1347; A-side Matrix # CHR 1347-8 AS
        - Hartman, Dan - Relight my fire, 1979; SR-26514; Hartman, Dan (Box 37)
          Catalog # JZ 36302; A-side Matrix # BL-36302-1Q
          Blue Sky
        - Hathaway, Donny - Come back Charleston blue, 1972; SR-26515; Hathaway, Donny; Jones, Quincy (Box 37)
          Catalog # SD 7010; A-side Matrix # ST-C 722579B
        - Haus-a-holics - Mete y saca, 1996; SR-26516; Haus-a-holics (Box 37)
          Catalog # UR 0119; A-side Matrix # UR0119 A1
          Upstairs Records
          San Jose, California
        - Hausfrauen - Midnight rain, 1981; SR-26517; Hausfrauen (Box 37)
          Catalog # BIG 2; A-side Matrix # BIG-2-A
          Cachalot Records
        - Hayes, Isaac - Hot buttered soul, 1969; SR-26518; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # SXE 005; A-side Matrix # DMB-9137 A-2/2-90 C
        - Hayes, Isaac - Lifetime thing, 1981; SR-26519; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # PD-1-6329; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6329-AS-PW
        - Hayes, Isaac - U-turn, 1986; SR-26520; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # C 40316; A-side Matrix # AL-40316-1B
        - Hayes, Isaac - Hotbed, 1978; SR-26521; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # STX-4102; A-side Matrix # STX-4102-A
        - Hayes, Isaac - The Isaac Hayes movement, 1985; SR-26522; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # SXE 025; A-side Matrix # DMF-2528 A-2/2-90
        - Hayes, Isaac - Don't let go, 1979; SR-26523; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # PD-1-6224-A; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6224-AS-AS-K-1
        - Hayes, Isaac - Hot buttered soul, 1969; SR-26524; Hayes, Isaac (Box 37)
          Catalog # ENS-1001; A-side Matrix # ENL-0069
          Enterprise
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Haza, Ofra - Yemenite songs, 1986; SR-26525; Haza, Ofra (Box 37)
          Catalog # EFA 6115; A-side Matrix # 1986115-WX 30. 730-A
          Ausfahrt
        - Head East - Head East live! (Disc one), 1979; SR-26526; Head East (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26527. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-6007; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 19031-P2
        - Head East - Head East live! (Disc two), 1979; SR-26527; Head East (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26526. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-6008; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 19032-P1
        - Headnodic - Tuesday, 2002; SR-26528; Headnodic (Box 37)
          Catalog # IUR-9010; A-side Matrix # S-50326 IUR-9010 1E
        - Headrillaz - The right way, 1998; SR-26529; Headrillaz (Box 37)
          Catalog # VVR5002336; A-side Matrix # VVR5002336-A1
          V2
        - Heir To The Throne - Hearts desire, 1991; SR-26530; Heir To The Throne (Box 37)
          Catalog # SWS-1008; A-side Matrix # SWS-1008-A
          Southway Records
        - Heat - Skatedance; Jammin', 1979; SR-26531; Heat (Box 37)
          Catalog # SM12-401; A-side Matrix # SM-12-401-A
          SMI
        - Heaven & Earth - I feel a groove under my feet, 1979; SR-26532; Heaven & Earth (Box 37)
          Catalog # MK-109; A-side Matrix # MK-109-A1-1-11
        - Heineken Pan Vibes Steel Orchestra - Carnival with steel 76, 1976; SR-26533; Heineken Pan Vibes Steel Orchestra (Box 37)
          Catalog # KDS-2010; A-side Matrix # KDS-2010-S1
          Kalinda
          Mount Albert, Ontario
        - Hemlock - Body rhythm, 1979; SR-26534; Hemlock (Box 37)
          Catalog # DWBS 8878; A-side Matrix # DWBS-8878-XCA-8875-V-S-M1
        - Hempstead High - A+, 1998; SR-26535; Hempstead High (Box 37)
          Catalog # U-53221; A-side Matrix # U-53221-A-RE1
          Universal Records
        - Henderson, Eddie - This band is hot; Moon, 1979; SR-26536; Henderson, Eddie (Box 37)
          Catalog # SPRO-9283; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9283 G1 (95942)
        - Henderson, Joe - Black Narcissus, 1976; SR-26537; Henderson, Joe (Box 37)
          Catalog # M-9071; A-side Matrix # M9071A FML1018760T CRP PIT#1
        - Henderson, Michael - Do it to me good (tonight), 1986; SR-26538; Henderson, Michael (Box 37)
          Catalog # V-19207; A-side Matrix # V-1-19207-Z1 Q B-22738-Z1
          EMI America
        - Henderson, Wayne - Living on a dream, 1978; SR-26539; Henderson, Wayne (Box 37)
          Catalog # PD-1-6145; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6145-BS-CP2
        - Hendrix, Jimi - The Jimi Hendrix concerts (Disc one), 1982; SR-26540; Hendrix, Jimi (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26541. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 88592; A-side Matrix # CBS.88592.A1
        - Hendrix, Jimi - The Jimi Hendrix concerts (Disc two), 1982; SR-26541; Hendrix, Jimi (Box 37)
          In same jacket as # SR-26540. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 88592; A-side Matrix # CBS.88592.C1
        - Hendrix, Jimi - Hendrix in the west, 1971; SR-26542; Hendrix, Jimi; Kramer, Eddie (Box 37)
          Catalog # 2302018; A-side Matrix # 2302018 A//1▽420 13 7
        - Hendrix, Jimi - Isle of Wright, 1971; SR-26543; Hendrix, Jimi; Jeffery, Michael (Box 38)
          Catalog # 2302016; A-side Matrix # 2302016 A//1▽420 1 1 3
        - Hendryx, Nona - Nona, 1983; SR-26544; Hendryx, Nona (Box 38)
          Catalog # AFL1-4565; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4565-A-RCA-2
        - Henry, Denard - Super Bleifrei EP, 1998; SR-26545; Henry, Denard (Box 38)
          Catalog # MUELLER2015; A-side Matrix # Muller 2015 cut b2 poce
          Müller Records
          Berlin, Germany
        - Henry, Freddy - Get it out in the open, 1979; SR-26546; Henry, Freddy (Box 38)
          Catalog # CL-8809; A-side Matrix # CL-8809-A PW
          Clouds
        - Herbaliser - New & improved; Theme from control centre, 1997; SR-26547; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          Seems to be in the wrong cover
          Catalog # ZEN 1251; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1251 A-1-1-2
        - Herbaliser - Scratchy noise, 1995; SR-26548; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          Catalog # ZEN 1234; A-side Matrix # ZEN.1234 A1
        - Herbaliser - Blow your headphones (Disc one), 1997; SR-26549; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26550. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 28; A-side Matrix # ZEN 28 A-01-1-1
        - Herbaliser - Blow your headphones (Disc two), 1997; SR-26550; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26549. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 28; A-side Matrix # ZEN 28 C-01-1-1
        - Herbaliser - Remedies (Disc one), 1995; SR-26551; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26552. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 18; A-side Matrix # MPO ZEN 18 A3
        - Herbaliser - Remedies (Disc two), 1995; SR-26552; Herbaliser (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26551. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 18; A-side Matrix # MPO ZEN 18 C2
        - Hewett, Howard - Forever and ever, 1988; SR-26553; Hewett, Howard (Box 38)
          Catalog # 60779-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60779-A 1
        - Hi Ba-se - Start 2 F..k, 1996; SR-26554; Hi Ba-se; Merlin; Smooth Joe (Box 38)
          Catalog # LHP 0196; A-side Matrix # LHP 0196 A
          Lucky House Productions
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Hi-Gloss - Hi-gloss, 1981; SR-26555; Hi-Gloss (Box 38)
          Catalog # PRL 12185 AS; A-side Matrix # PRL-12185A-REI-1A
        - Hi-Tension - Hi-tension; Girl I betcha, 1978; SR-26556; Hi-Tension (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26557. 2 copies.
          Catalog # IS 1010; A-side Matrix # IS 1010A-1A
        - Hi-Tension - Hi-tension; Girl I betcha, 1978; SR-26557; Hi-Tension (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26556. 2 copies.
        - High Inergy - Frenzy, 1979; SR-26558; High Inergy (Box 38)
          Catalog # G7-989R1; A-side Matrix # G7-989R1A-18A
          Gordy
        - High Lonesome Sound System - Champion sound remixes (Disc one), 1998; SR-26559; High Lonesome Sound System (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26560. Double album.
          Catalog # Exist Dance 017; A-side Matrix # L-49608
          Exist Dance
        - High Lonesome Sound System - Champion sound remixes (Disc two), 1998; SR-26560; High Lonesome Sound System (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26559. Double album.
        - High Lonesome Sound System - Champion sound remixes (Disc one), 1998; SR-26561; High Lonesome Sound System (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26562. Double album.
        - High Lonesome Sound System - Champion sound remixes (Disc two), 1998; SR-26562; High Lonesome Sound System (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26561. Double album.
        - High, Martha - Martha High, 1979; SR-26563; High, Martha (Box 38)
          Catalog # SA 8526; A-side Matrix # SA-8526-A-10
        - Highland Place Mobsters - 1746DCGA30035 (Disc one), 1992; SR-26564; Highland Place Mobsters (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26565. Double album.
          Catalog # 73008-26004-1; A-side Matrix # 73008 26004-1-SA-SP1
          LaFace Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Highland Place Mobsters - 1746DCGA30035 (Disc two), 1992; SR-26565; Highland Place Mobsters (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26564. Double album.
          Catalog # 73008-26004-1; A-side Matrix # 73008 26004-1-SC-SP1
        - Hip Hop Junkies - Da Hip Hop Junkies, 1997; SR-26566; Hip Hop Junkies; Davey Dex (Box 38)
          Catalog # AV35; A-side Matrix # AV 35 A
          AV8 Records
        - Hipsway - The honeythief, 1986; SR-26567; Hipsway (Box 38)